Guide to the Edward Scott-Snell papers M3007
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
- At Kelmscott Manor, 1885-1988
  - Stephani Scott-Snell, "Thessyros" 2nd state, undated; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 641)
  - Martin Knowles, Scott-Snell and Fell geneologies, undated (Box 11, Folder 642)
  - Stephani & Edward Scott-Snell, Exhibition catalogue, no year October 1944; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 643)
  - Winifred Whitehead, Wimbledon, 1885-1965; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 644)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, Exhibition terms, 1936 January 15; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 645)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, Exhibition scheduling, 1936 February 15; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 646)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, Exhibition Catalogue, 1936 May; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 647)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, Exhibition advertisement receipt, 1936 June 1; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 648)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, Exhibition sales statement, 1936 July 10; 4 pages (Box 11, Folder 649)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, Exhibition mounting receipt, 1937 February 24; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 650)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, bill from Oxford Mail with his autograph apology, 1936 June 1; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 651)
  - ALS from Alan L. Houghton to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 652)
  - ALS from Alan L. Houghton to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 653)
  - TLS from Speechly, Mumford & Craig to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 October 25; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 654)
  - Alan Houghton & Edward Scott-Snell, Debenture, 1933 November 6; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 655)
  - TLS from Alan L. Houghton to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 November 17; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 656)
  - TLS from Alan Houghton to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 December 23; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 657)
  - ALS from Alan L. Houghton to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 June 14; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 658)
  - TLS from Wilfrid H. Hulbert to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 June 16; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 659)
  - TLS from Speechly, Mumford & Craig to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 July 10; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 660)
  - TLS from Wilfrid H. Hulbert to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 July 23; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 661)
  - TLS from Speechly, Mumford & Craig to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 August 7; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 662)
  - TLS from Speechly, Mumford & Craig to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 August 13; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 663)
  - TLS from Wilfrid H. Hulbert to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 August 17; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 664)
  - TLU from [Houghton] Rubinstein, Nash & Co. to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 August 19; 5 pages (Box 11, Folder 665)
  - TLU from Speechly, Mumford & Craig to Houghton & Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 August 20; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 666)
  - TLS from Speechly, Mumford & Craig to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 August 20; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 667)
  - TLS from Speechly, Mumford & Craig to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 August 21; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 668)
  - TLS from Speechly, Mumford & Craig to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 August 26; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 669)
  - TLS from Speechly, Mumford & Craig to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 September 10; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 670)
  - ALS from Alan L. Houghton to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 September 23; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 671)
  - TLS from Speechly, Mumford & Craig to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 September 28; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 672)
  - TLS from Speechly, Mumford & Craig to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 September 30; 3 pages (Box 11, Folder 673)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, Testimonial from R.P. Longden with Edward Scott-Snell's edited version, 1940 May 28; 2 pages (Box 11, Folder 674)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, Testimonial from Randolph Schwabe, 1940 May 17; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 675)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, Testimonial from H. Lionel Rogers, undated; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 676)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, Testimonial from H. Lionel Rogers, 1940 May 20; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 677)
  - Edward Godwin, Testimonial from Merchant Taylor's School, 1947 November 15; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 678)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, Testimonial from Albert Rutherston, 1940 May 17; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 679)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, Testimonial from Radley College, 1940 August 7; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 680)
  - Edward Scott-Snell, Testimonial from Christ's Hospital, 1944 September 30; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 681)
  - ALS from A.E. Money to Joscelyn Godwin, 1988 November 11; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 682)
  - Edward Godwin, Curriculum vitae, 1965; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 683)
  - Edward Godwin, State Teachers Certificate, 1967 June 13; 1 page (Box 11, Folder 684)